American Council for Emigres in the Professions; Records ger017
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP, Undated; 4; originals - 1160 individual files
  - Salin, Edgar, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 54)
  - Salinger, Gerhard, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 55)
  - de Salles Oliveira, Armando, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 56)
  - Salomon, Willy, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 57)
  - Salvatorelli, Luigi, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 58)
  - Samter, Marion E., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 59)
  - Samuel, Ernst, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 60)
  - Sanchez-Albornoz, Claudio, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 61)
  - Sand, Rene, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 62)
  - Santalo, Miguel, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 63)
  - Sapir, Boris, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 64)
  - Saragat, Giuseppe, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 65)
  - Sarankievich, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 66)
  - Sarason, David, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 67)
  - Sartre, Jean Paul, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 68)
  - Saybert, Blanche & Salvatore, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 69)
  - Scelle, Georges, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 70)
  - Schacht, Joseph, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 71)
  - Schaefer, B. W., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 72)
  - Schayer, Stanislaw, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 73)
  - Scheerer, Martin, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 74)
  - Schenk, Karl, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 75)
  - Schiff, Walter, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 76)
  - Schilling, Edmund, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 77)
  - Schindler, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 78)
  - de Schlozer, Boris, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 79)
  - Schmidl-Waehner, Trude, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 80)
  - Schmidt, Karl, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 81)
  - Schneiderman, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 82)
  - Schnurmann, Else, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 83)
  - Schoeps, Hans-Joachim, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 84)
  - Schottlaender, Hilde, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 85)
  - Schouten, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 86)
  - Schrade, Leo, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 87)
  - Schrecker, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 88)
  - Schuck, Walter, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 89)
  - Schuhl, Pierre Maime, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 90)
  - Schulhoff, Otto, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 91)
  - Schultz, Fritz, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 92)
  - Schwann, Constantin, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 93)
  - Schwartz, Jacques, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 94)
  - Schwarz, Andreas B., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 95)
  - Schwarz, Ernst, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 96)
  - Schwarz, Heinrich, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 97)
  - Schwarz, Robert, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 98)
  - Schwarzbart, Adolf, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 99)
  - Schwarzwald, Eugenia, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 100)
  - Schweinburg, Fritz, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 101)
  - Schweitzer, Ernest Emil, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 102)
  - Seckel, Alfred, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 103)
  - Segal, Arthur, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 104)
  - Segre, Beniamino, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 105)
  - Segre, Mario, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 106)
  - Segre, Umberto, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 107)
  - Sels, Otto, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 108)
  - Semmingsen, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 109)
  - Serge, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 110)
  - Serra Baldo, Alfonso, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 111)
  - Serrail, Jean, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 112)
  - Seta, Della, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 113)
  - Shakhmatoff, Mstislav, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 114)
  - Shluger, Alexander, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 115)
  - Siegfried, Andre, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 116)
  - Sierpinski, Waclair, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 117)
  - Silone, Ignazio, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 118)
  - Simchowitz, Herman, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 119)
  - Simoes, Jacinto, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 120)
  - Simon, Alicia, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 121)
  - Simon, Erich E., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 122)
  - Simon, Hans, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 123)
  - Simon, Josef, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 124)
  - Simons, Gerda, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 125)
  - Simons, Hellmuth, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 126)
  - Singer, Hans W., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 127)
  - Singer, Kurt (Economics), Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 128)
  - Singer, Kurt (Music), Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 129)
  - Singer, Rolf, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 130)
  - Sinzheimer, Hugo, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 131)
  - Sinzheimer, Ursula Doris, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 132)
  - Skoumal, Aloys, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 133)
  - Skutsch, Otto, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 134)
  - Sladek, T. W., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 135)
  - Slotty, Friedrich, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 136)
  - Smetana, Julius, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 137)
  - Snapper, Frits, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 138)
  - Solari, Juan Antonio, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 139)
  - Soldevila, Fernando, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 140)
  - Sommerfelt, Alf, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 141)
  - Somogyi-Schill, Stefan de, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 142)
  - Sontag, E., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 143)
  - Soudek, Josef, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 144)
  - Soustelle, Jacques, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 145)
  - Spanjer, Albert, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 146)
  - Speter, Max, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 147)
  - Speyer, Hermine, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 148)
  - Spiegel, Kathe, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 149)
  - Spirer, Alexander, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 150)
  - Spitzer, Berthold, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 151)
  - Spitzer, Hermann Maria, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 152)
  - Spitzer, Tadeusz, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 153)
  - Spranger, Edward, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 154)
  - Sraffa, Piero, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 155)
  - Staudinger, Hans, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 156)
  - Stechert, Kurt, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 157)
  - Stein, Edmund, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 158)
  - Stein, Ernest, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 159)
  - Stein, Harry, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 160)
  - Steinach, Eugen, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 161)
  - Steinberg, Witold, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 162)
  - Steindl, Josef, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 163)
  - Steinen, Diether von den, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 164)
  - Steiner, Ernst, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 165)
  - Steiner, Herbert, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 166)
  - Steinschneider, Adolf, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 167)
  - Steinthal, Hans, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 168)
  - Stern, Eric, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 169)
  - Stern, Fritz, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 170)
  - Stern, Hans, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 171)
  - Stern, Henri, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 172)
  - Sterneck, Berthold, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 173)
  - Sternheimer, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 174)
  - Stiassny, Melanie, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 175)
  - Stieler, Hilde, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 176)
  - Stöcker, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 177)
  - Stoessel, Franz, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 178)
  - Stöhr, Richard, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 179)
  - Storch, Alfred, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 1)
  - Strauss, Karl, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 2)
  - Strecker, Reinhard, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 3)
  - Stremooukhoff, Dimitri, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 4)
  - Strich, Fritz, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 5)
  - Strigl, Richard von, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 6)
  - Strupp, Karl, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 7)
  - Struve, Gleb Petrovich, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 8)
  - Strzemienski, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 9)
  - Studencki, Stanislas M., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 10)
  - Stumbergs, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 11)
  - Sturmthal, Adolf, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 12)
  - Stutterheim, William F., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 13)
  - Sühnel, Rudolf R., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 14)
  - Sulkowski, Joseph, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 15)
  - Sultan, Herbert, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 16)
  - Surroca, Martinez, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 17)
  - Sussmann, Toni, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 18)
  - Swoboda, Frank, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 19)
  - Syrkus, Helena & Szymon P., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 20)
  - Szalai, Tibo, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 21)
  - Szeftel, Moise, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 22)
  - Szekely, Edmond, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 23)
  - Szende, Zoltan, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 24)
  - Szturm de Sztrem, Edward, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 25)
  - Szuecz, Josef, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 26)
  - Tagliacozzo, Giorgio, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 27)
  - Tandler, Julius, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 28)
  - Tasca, Angelo, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 29)
  - Tatarkiewiez, Wladislaus, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 30)
  - Täubler, Ernst, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 31)
  - Tellez Plasencia, Heliodoro, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 32)
  - Terrasse, Henri Louis Etienne, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 33)
  - Thalheimer, August, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 34)
  - Thiringer, William von, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 35)
  - Thorbecke, W. J. R., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 36)
  - Tinbergen, Johann, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 37)
  - Tisza, Ladislas, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 38)
  - Titov, Alexander, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 39)
  - Tonnelat, Ernest, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 40)
  - Torner, Eduardo Martinez, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 41)
  - Trampczynski, Witold, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 42)
  - Trentin, Silvio, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 43)
  - Treves, Paolo, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 44)
  - Treves, Piero, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 45)
  - Treviranus, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 46)
  - Trias, Joaquin, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 47)
  - Tritsch, Walter, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 48)
  - Truptil, Roger, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 49)
  - Tur, Ramon Medina, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 50)
  - Turan, Paul, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 51)
  - Tzara, Tristan, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 52)
  - Unbegaun, Boris, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 53)
  - Urbsiene, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 54)
  - Urias, Alfred, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 55)
  - Utitz, Emil, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 56)
  - Vago, George, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 57)
  - Van Creveld, S., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 58)
  - Vandel, Rene, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 59)
  - Van den Bergh, Georg, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 60)
  - Van der Leeuw, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 61)
  - Van der Meulen, Theodore, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 62)
  - Vaucher, Paul, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 63)
  - Ventura, Rafael S., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 64)
  - Vera, Francusco, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 65)
  - Vergara, Eddy, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 66)
  - Vermeil, Edmond, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 67)
  - Verzijl, Jan Hendrik Willem, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 68)
  - Vetter, Hans A., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 69)
  - Victor, Paul-Emile, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 70)
  - Vieth, J., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 71)
  - Vieyra, Maurice, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 72)
  - Viterbo, Camillo, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 73)
  - Vivante, Leone, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 74)
  - Vleeschhouwer, J. E., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 75)
  - Vocadlo, Otakar, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 76)
  - Vogt, Hans, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 77)
  - Volbach, Wolfgang F., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 78)
  - Volterra, Edoardo, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 79)
  - Vysheskavzeff, Boris, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 80)
  - Wable, Karl, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 81)
  - Wachlowski, Zenon, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 82)
  - Wachsmann, Klaus, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 83)
  - Wachtel, Curt, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 84)
  - Waismann, Friedrich, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 85)
  - Wajsblum, Marc, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 86)
  - Waldheim, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 87)
  - Walzer, Richard, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 88)
  - Wallerstein, Lothar, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 89)
  - Warnier, Raymond, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 90)
  - Waterman, H. I., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 91)
  - Wauters, Arthur, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 92)
  - Weichbrodt, Rafael (Ralph), Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 93)
  - Weidle, Wladimir, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 94)
  - Weigert, Fritz, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 95)
  - Weil, Benno, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 96)
  - Weill, Georges, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 97)
  - Weinberg, Dagmar, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 98)
  - Weinberg, Siegfried, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 99)
  - Weinberger, Otto, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 100)
  - Weinreich, Max, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 101)
  - Weinstock, Stephan, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 102)
  - Weisl, Millicent, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 103)
  - Weisl, Wolfgang von, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 104)
  - Weiss, F. X., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 105)
  - Weiss, Franz Josef, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 106)
  - Weiss, Helene, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 107)
  - Weiss, Hilde, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 108)
  - Weiss, Jakob, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 109)
  - Weiss, M. Jakob, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 110)
  - Weiss, Paul, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 111)
  - Weissenberg, Julius Richard, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 112)
  - Weissmann, Irma, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 113)
  - Werfel, Franz, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 114)
  - Werner, Othmar, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 115)
  - Wertenstein, Louis (Ludwik), Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 116)